http://www.teachersource.com/category/privacy

FREE Economy Ground SHIPPING on orders over $99! (Prepaid orders only. Restrictions apply.)
WE BUILD CUSTOM KITS!
Join the Kids' Science Club
Material Safety Data Sheets (MSDS)
Contact Us
FREE Economy Ground SHIPPING on orders over $99! (Prepaid orders only. Restrictions apply.)
Watch Our Workshop Videos
3-2-1 Blast Off!
What The Heck Happened?!?!
Cool, Can We Do That Again?
Join the Kids' Science Club
Material Safety Data Sheets (MSDS)
Join the Kids' Science Club
Material Safety Data Sheets (MSDS)
Contact Us
NEW!
K-3
[266]
3-5
[387]
5-8
[540]
9-12
[497]
College
[367]
Visit the Newsletter Library
[496]
Free Lesson Ideas
Search for NGSS Correlations
Watch Our Workshop Videos
[133]
Webinars
Join the Kids' Science Club
Material Safety Data Sheets (MSDS)
Science Fair Supplies
[57]
Kid Friendly Science
[282]
For Homeschoolers
[441]
Home Science Lab
Science Fair Ideas
[101]
Science Parties
[48]
Gift Certificates
[2]
Privacy & Security
Educational Innovations, Inc. takes your privacy very seriously.  We will never give or sell your private information to other companies without first seeking your permission.  We have created this Privacy Policy to illustrate our firm commitment to protecting your personal information.  The following discloses our information gathering and collecting practices relating to our website (www.TeacherSource.com).  If you have any questions about the practices described here, see “How to contact us” below.
This Privacy Policy will be effective as of May 24, 2018 for all new users and users in EU and EEA member countries.  For all other users, this Privacy Policy will be effective on June 23, 2018.
Topics:
What is personal information?
What information do we collect about you?
How will we use your information?
Marketing
Access to your information and correction
Cookies
Other websites
Changes to our privacy policy
How to contact us
What is personal information?
“Personal information” means information that specifically identifies an individual person, such as name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or account number.  It may also include other information about you, such as gender, date of birth, or other demographic information, or about your use of the website, such as IP address or cookies, if that other information is linked to your personal information.
What information do we collect about you?
We collect personal information that you provide to us when you register with our website or place an order for our products.  We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback, or participate in our occasional competitions.  Our website includes customer reviews for many of our products.  We will only post these reviews with your consent.
How will we use your information?
We use your information collected from the website to personalize your repeat visits to our website.  We may also use your personal information to:
respond to your requests, comments or concerns;
conduct and administer user testing and surveys as well as sweepstakes, competitions and similar promotions;
provide you with relevant promotional messages and other useful information about our products, blogs, free lessons, sales and similar promotions;
assist you in managing your account or process your order; or
comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Educational Innovations will never share your information with third parties, unless it is:
with your consent;
in connection with a sale, merger, acquisition or corporate reorganization
to fulfill a legal obligation, such as in response to lawful requests or legal process, including in response to law enforcement requirements; or as part of a business transaction, sale or transfer, or bankruptcy proceeding;
for protection of personal or public safety or to prevent illegal activities; or
to protect our own rights including enforcing our own policies, contracts, and terms of use.
Marketing
We would like to send you information about products, lessons or blogs which may be of interest to you.  If you request to be on our newsletter mailing list, we will send you special product updates and exclusive discount offers that are not available to non-subscribers.  You'll also receive $5 off your next $50 order.
If you have consented to receive marketing, you always have the opportunity to opt out of our marketing communications with you or change your preferences by following a link in the footer of all non-transactional email messages from us or by emailing us at newsletters@TeacherSource.com.
Some communications from us are considered transactional or service communications (for example, important account notifications and billing information.  Even if you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, we may still contact you concerning a transaction or purchase.
Access to your information and correction
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you.  We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date.  You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please send your request in writing to:
Educational Innovations, Inc.
5 Francis J. Clarke Circle
Bethel CT 06801 USA
Cookies
Website usage information is collected using cookies.  Like many other websites, we ask you to allow us to use cookies to remember information about you and improve your browsing experience on our site.  If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas may be limited.
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information.  This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
For more information about cookies, including how to set your internet browser to reject cookies, please go to www.allaboutcookies.org or www.networkadvertising.org.  You can set your browser not to accept cookies; these websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser.  However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.
Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites.  This privacy policy only applies to www.TeacherSource.com.  When you link to other websites, you should read their own privacy policies.
Protection of your personal information
Educational Innovations, Inc. uses industry-standard security techniques to help protect the personal information that we collect from you on our website.  We maintain secure facilities protected by firewalls and other security devices.  These measures are designed to protect your information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration.  We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.  However, despite these reasonable precautions, we do not guarantee that information transmitted through the internet is secure, or that such transmissions will be free from delay, interruption, or error.  We also do not guarantee that the information will remain secure against theft or misuse.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page.  This privacy policy was last updated on May 24, 2018.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.  You can email us at newsletters@TeacherSource.com or send written correspondence to:
Educational Innovations, Inc.
5 Francis J. Clarke Circle
Bethel CT 06801 USA
Follow us
Sign up for our Email NewsletterLearn More
Enter Email
We use cookies to offer an improved online experience and offer you content and services adapted to your interests. By using our site, you are giving your consent to
our cookie policy.
I Understand
